freegayhostgalleries.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy

#### Data Security Statement

At Media Mania LLC we follow the best advisable practices for maintaining the security and integrity of our users' and members' personal information:

All order information from transactions in our online store- credit card data as well as address and other personal information- is processed via SSL encrypted data transfer. The most current security updates and upgrades are applied to our servers to prevent unauthorized access to our computer systems. Access to customers' personal information is restricted to only authorized Media Mania LLC personnel. Access to credit card number data is limited to the last four digits of the number and is used by Customer Service solely for the purposes of verification in communication with the customer.

#### Privacy Policy

We at Media Mania LLC take your privacy very seriously. We want you to be able to enjoy our adult bear entertainment without fearing that your privacy will be violated or your information shared inappropriately.

Media Mania LLC want to assure you that we do not sell or make available user information provided via our web site(s) to third parties except as specified in this Privacy Policy. User Information may be made available to or at the direction of legal and regulatory authorities (including tax authorities) if required by the public authorities as well as to Media Mania LLC's professional advisers subject to professional obligations for data confidentiality. We are firmly committed to guarding the confidence you have placed in us and to use any information you volunteer responsibly and professionally. If you do not want to share personal data, please read below for information on how to opt out or change personal information Media Mania LLC collects from you.

#### Sharing Information with Other Entities

Media Mania LLC reserve the right to share customer data with Media Mania LLC's subsidiaries,  contractors, third party billing processors and temporary employees but only for the purpose of fulfilling its legitimate business interests as described in this Privacy Policy. Additionally, Media Mania LLC reserves the right to transfer customer data to other entities as part of business transactions such as, but not limited to, spinoffs, acquisitions, mergers, reorganizations or liquidations. With your permission, Media Mania LLC may share your information with some of our valued partners. Please see the opt-in box on our subscription form. If you check that box, Media Mania LLC may allow partners to contact you via email with products or services that we think might be of interest to our customers.

#### Email Newsletters

Media Mania LLC distributes various topic specific newsletters. We require first name and last name, so that we may personalize your greeting, email address and in some cases your country, as not all offers are valid in all countries. Typically all other contact information is voluntary and may be used to send other information or offers via mail. We do not share your information with third parties, except as required to deliver our message.

#### Unsubscribing/Opt-Out

We frequently provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and/or our partners at the point where we request your information. Also, in our email communications you will find instructions for unsubscribing.

#### Information We Automatically Collect

For each web visitor we record date & time of visit, IP address and browser type to analyze how visitors use our site and to gather broad demographic information like country of origin and browser usage among our visitors. This information will not be matched against your personal information as supplied through all the means disclosed above. This information is analyzed and then purged on a regular basis.

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of these linked sites, because their privacy practices may differ from ours.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of text asking permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. If you agree, then your browser adds the text in a small file. Cookies allow a web application to respond to you as an individual and distinguish you from other visitors on the site at the same time. Cookies do not allow us to determine personal information about you.

#### Privacy and Children

Media Mania LLC and the Media Mania LLC web sites do not target children (defined as those persons under 18 years of age) as an audience or a market. Media Mania LLC intends to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child we will make all -reasonable efforts to delete that data from our records.

For additional information on Children's Privacy, please see: http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/topics/kids-online-safety
